이 노래는 It's about you baby
Only you
You you you you you you you
내가 힘들 때 울 것 같을 때
기운도 이제 나지 않을 때
It's you
날 걱정하네
날 웃게 하네
말 안 해도 돼
Boy what do you say
멀리선 언제든지 달려와
(They keep on asking me, "who is he?")
바쁜 척도 없이 넌 나타나
이게 말이 되니
날 물어봐
( They keep on asking me, "who is he?")
너는 말야
he's the one that's living in my system, baby
Oh my oh my god
예상했어 나
I was really hoping
That he will come through
Oh my oh my god
단 너뿐이야
Asking all the time
About what I should do
Now I'm asking
No, I can never let him go
너만 생각나 24
난 행운아야
정말로 I know I know
널 알기 전까지는 나
의미 없었어
전부 다 내 맘이
끝이 없는 걸
I know I know
I'm going crazy right
어디서든
몇 번이든
There ain't nothing else that I would hold on to
I hear his voice
through all the noise
잠시라도 내 손 놓지 마
걱정 없잖아
Cause I got someone
혼자라도 괜찮아
Cause I love someone
(They keep on asking me, "who is he?")
멀리든 언제든지 달려와
바쁜 척도 없이 넌 나타나
(They keep on asking me, "who is he?")
"이게 말이 되니?" 난 물어봐
너는 말야
He's the one that's livin' in my system, baby
Oh my oh my god
예상했어 나
I was really hoping
That he will come through
Oh my oh my god
단 너 뿐이야
Asking all the time
About what I should do
No I can never let him go
나만 생각나 24
난 행운아야 정말로
I know I know
널 알기 전까지는 나
의미 없었어 전부 다
내 맘이 끝이 없는 걸
I know I know
He's the one that's living in my system
Baby baby baby baby baby
I'm goin' crazy right
Baby baby I'm goin' crazy right
Baby baby baby baby
너와 나
My heart is glowin' it's glowin' up
너랑만 있으면 무서울 게 없어
가득 메워진, 다 메워진
My heart is glowing, it'd be glowing
Cause he
Oh my oh my god
예상했어 나
I was really hoping
That he will come through
Oh my oh my god
단 너 뿐이야
Asking all the time
About what I should do
No I can never let him go
He's right there for me 24
난 행운아야 정말로
I know I know
널 알기 전까지는 나
의미 없었어 전부 다
My heart is glowin' it's glowin'
My heart is glowin' up so
I can't sleep at night